Guide to the Heather Lewis Papers 1965-2002 (Bulk 1980-1999) MSS 132 MSS.132
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: House Rules
  - Subseries E: Publicity Materials
    - QPB Review. House Rules mentioned in Editorical Director's letter and a listing., 1996 (Box 6, Folder 148)
    - Reviews of House Rules, additional materials in oversize box., 1994 (Box 6, Folder 149)
    - Serpent's Tail book catalogues, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 150)
    - Special to the New York Times, undated (Box 6, Folder 151)
    - Secker and Warburg advertisement featuring House Rules, undated (Box 6, Folder 152)
    - Secker and Warburg. Minerva: New Books, July-December 1994. House Rules included. (Box 6, Folder 153)
    - Village Voice, vol 39 no 40. October 4, 1994. Review of House Rules. Original located in oversize box. (Box 6, Folder 154)
- Series IV: Second Suspect
  This series includes manuscripts, publication materials and publicity from Heather Lewis's second novel, The Second Suspect. The series is divided into three subseries: Subseries A: Manuscripts, Subseries b: Publication materials and Subseries C: Publicity Materials.
  - Subseries A: Manuscripts
    - Acknowledgements, undated (Box 6, Folder 155)
    - Second Suspect Outline, undated (Box 6, Folder 156)
    - Second Suspect, Draft Chapter 1, undated (Box 6, Folder 157)
    - The Second Suspect, Draft p. 1-301, undated (Box 7, Folder 158)
    - Second Suspect, Draft p. 4-293, undated (Box 7, Folder 159)
    - Second Suspect, Draft p. 1-291 with annotations, undated (Box 7, Folder 160)
    - Second Suspect, incomplete draft. p. 62-264 with annotations, undated (Box 7, Folder 161)
    - The Second Suspect, incomplete draft p. 1-204., undated (Box 7, Folder 162)
    - The Second Suspect, draft p. 1-197 with annotations, undated (Box 7, Folder 163)
    - The Second Suspect, draft p. 1-182., undated (Box 7, Folder 164)
    - The Second Suspect, draft fragment p. 1, 113-225, 258-291, undated (Box 7, Folder 165)
    - The Second Suspect, draft fragment p. 1-151. Chapters 1-17, undated (Box 7, Folder 166)
    - The Second Suspect, draft fragment p. 1-119. Chapters 1-10, undated (Box 7, Folder 167)
    - The Second Suspect, draft fragment p. 163-294., undated (Box 7, Folder 168)
    - The Second Suspect, draft fragment p. 16-113. Includes one page biography at the end., undated (Box 7, Folder 169)
    - The Second Suspect,draft p. 1-99. Titled "Restitution"., undated (Box 7, Folder 170)
    - The Second Suspect,draft fragment, "one-nine" p. 1-99., undated (Box 7, Folder 171)
    - The Second Suspect, draft fragment. p. 1-56, 78-144, 146-151., undated (Box 7, Folder 172)
    - The Second Suspect, draft fragment, titled "Restitution" p. 1-66., undated (Box 7, Folder 173)
    - The Second Suspect, draft fragment p. 1-53, undated (Box 7, Folder 174)
    - The Second Suspect,draft fragment p. 1-39., undated (Box 7, Folder 175)
    - The Second Suspect, titled "Restitution" p. 1-23., undated (Box 7, Folder 176)
    - The Second Suspect, draft fragment titled "Restitution" Chapter 1 p. 1-14., undated (Box 7, Folder 177)
    - The Second Suspect, draft fragment p. 11-18, undated (Box 7, Folder 178)
    - The Second Suspect,draft fragment 109-111, undated (Box 7, Folder 179)
    - The Second Suspect,draft fragment p. 283-317., undated (Box 7, Folder 180)
    - The Second Suspect, Labeled "Thirteen" p. 139-150., undated (Box 7, Folder 181)
    - The Second Suspect, two copies labeled "Thirteen", undated (Box 8, Folder 182)
    - The Second Suspect, Labeled "Fifteen" p. 187-207, undated (Box 8, Folder 183)
    - The Second Suspect, early outline. Chapters 18-32., undated (Box 8, Folder 184)
    - The Second Suspect, Synopsis., undated (Box 8, Folder 185)
  - Subseries B: Publication Materials
    - Second Suspect cover art [proofs], undated (Box 8, Folder 186)
    - Second Suspect dust jackets. [see oversized box]., undated (Box 8, Folder 187)
    - Second susptect, publicity postcard proof, undated (Box 8, Folder 188)
    - The Second Suspect, Draft from copy editor to compositor. July 29, 1997. (Box 8, Folder 189)
    - The Second Suspect, photocopies of page proofs. September 23, 1997. (Box 8, Folder 190)
    - The Second Suspect, master set of page proofs. November 10, 1997. (Box 8, Folder 191)
    - The Second Suspect, revised page proofs #1. November 10, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 192)
    - The Second Suspect, fragments. June 15, 1998. (Box 8, Folder 193)
  - Subseries C: Publicity Matierals
    - Barnes and Noble online, Author interview with Heather Lewis. Thursday, January 13, 2000. (Box 8, Folder 194)
    - The Second Suspect. Doubleday Catalogue., 1998 (Box 8, Folder 195)
    - The Second Suspect, Murder Ink Catalogue., 1998 (Box 8, Folder 196)
    - The Second Suspect, Review OUT Magazine. June 1998. (Box 8, Folder 197)
    - The Second Suspect, publication announcement postcards., undated (Box 8, Folder 198)
    - The Second Suspect review, Publishers Weekly., 1998 (Box 8, Folder 199)
    - The Second Suspect, Reviews, ca. 1998 (Box 8, Folder 200)
- Series V: Notice
  This series contains manuscripts from Heather Lewis's novel Notice. Notice was Lewis's third novel, however it was not well received by publishers and she moved on to other projects. Serpent's Tail published Notice posthumously in 2004. The series begins with drafts Lewis titled "Wives," which later became "Notice".
  - "Wives" p. 1-12, undated (Box 8, Folder 201)
  - "Wives" p. 2-19, undated (Box 8, Folder 202)
  - "Wives" p. 1-13 with annotations, undated (Box 8, Folder 203)
  - "Wives" p. 1-12 with annotations, undated (Box 8, Folder 204)
  - "Wives" p. 1-11, undated (Box 8, Folder 205)
  - "Wives" p. 1-19, undated (Box 8, Folder 206)
  - Draft p. 2-271, undated (Box 8, Folder 207)
  - Notice, Draft p. 1-145. Chapters 1-17, undated (Box 8, Folder 208)
  - Notice, Draft p. 2-275 Chapters 1-31, undated (Box 8, Folder 209)
  - Notice, draft p. 146-265. Chapters 19-31, undated (Box 8, Folder 210)
  - Notice, draft p. 146-274. Chapters 19-, undated (Box 9, Folder 211)
  - Notice, draft p. 145-275. Chapters 19-, undated (Box 9, Folder 212)
  - Notice, p. 1-20. Chapter 9, undated (Box 9, Folder 213)
  - Notice draft chapter 9, p. 1-20, undated (Box 9, Folder 214)
  - Notice draft chapter 9, p. 1-14, undated (Box 9, Folder 215)
  - Notice draft chapter 18, p. 2-10, undated (Box 9, Folder 216)
  - Notice, draft chapter 18, p. 2-13, undated (Box 9, Folder 217)
  - Notice, draft chapter 18, p. 2-14, undated (Box 9, Folder 218)
  - Notice, draft chapter 19, p. 1-53, undated (Box 9, Folder 219)
  - Notice, draft p. 2-11, undated (Box 9, Folder 220)
  - Notice, draft p. 2-27, undated (Box 9, Folder 221)
  - Notice, draft chapter 13, undated (Box 9, Folder 222)
  - Draft fragment p. 2-6, undated (Box 9, Folder 223)
  - Draft fragment p. 15-20, undated (Box 9, Folder 224)
  - Draft fragment p. 2, 4-165, 167-273, undated (Box 9, Folder 225)
- Series VI: Other Writing
  This series includes Heather Lewis's other writing projects and is broken into five subseries. Subseries A contains short stories. Subseries B includes Lewis's writing from Sarah Lawrence College, particularly research papers. Subseries C contains poetry. Subseries D includes essays Lewis wrote as an adult and public letters. Subseries E: Miscellaneous includes an undated short paper on Martin Luther King Jr. and chapters from a possible fourth novel featuring Detective Reese. These materials are in chronological order where possible. Remaining materials are in alphabetical order.
  - Subseries A: Stories
    - Boulder Story with annotations, undated (Box 9, Folder 226)
    - Early Stories, titled "House Rules", undated (Box 9, Folder 227)
    - Story Fragment, undated (Box 9, Folder 228)
    - Story Fragments, possibly House Rules related. With annotations., undated (Box 9, Folder 229)
    - Writing Fragments. Titled "Taking Back" or "Restitution." Begins "It was the kind of dream...", undated (Box 9, Folder 230)
    - "Taking Back" draft, undated (Box 9, Folder 231)
  - Subseries B: Sarah Lawrence College
    - "Fear and Loathing of an Organ", 1986 (Box 9, Folder 232)
    - Interview permission forms, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 233)
    - Outline, Victorial Sexuality Conference Paper, undated (Box 9, Folder 234)
    - Student Evaluations by Faculty., 1983-1987 (Box 9, Folder 235)
    - Term Papers, undated (Box 9, Folder 236)
  - Subseries C: Poetry
    - Poetry 1978 (Box 9, Folder 237)
    - Poetry, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 238)
    - Poetry, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 239)
    - Poetry, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 240)
    - Poetry, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 241)
    - Poetry, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 242)
    - Poetry, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 243)
    - Poetry, undated (Box 9, Folder 244)
    - Poetry, unknown author. Likely Heather Lewis, undated (Box 9, Folder 245)
  - Subseries D: Essays, Letters
    - Introduction Best Lesbian Erotica, likely 1996, undated (Box 9, Folder 246)
    - Advertisement for Best Lesbian Erotica 1996, Pucker Up Magazine 1:2 (Box 9, Folder 247)
    - Draft "Looking Glass, Darkly" Review of End of Alice by A.M. Homes, undated (Box 9, Folder 248)
    - Draft "Looking Glass, Darkly" Review of End of Alice by A.M. Homes. With annotations, undated (Box 9, Folder 249)
    - Draft titled "I'll be Your Mirror", which later became "Looking Glass, Darkly". Review of End of Alice by A.M. Homes. With annotations., undated (Box 9, Folder 250)
    - Draft titled "I'll be Your Mirror", which later became "Looking Glass, Darkly". Review of End of Alice by A.M. Homes, undated (Box 9, Folder 251)
    - Draft titled "I'll be Your Mirror", which later became "Looking Glass, Darkly". Review of End of Alice by A.M. Homes, undated (Box 9, Folder 252)
    - Final "Looking Glass, Darkly". Review of End of Alice by A.M. Homes, undated (Box 9, Folder 250)
    - Voice Literary Supplement. March 1996. Includes "Looking Glass, Darkly." Original located in oversize box. (Box 9, Folder 251)
    - Response to panel description., undated (Box 9, Folder 252)
    - Drafts "Richard Nixon and Me", undated (Box 9, Folder 253)
  - Subseries E: Miscellaneous
    - Martin Luther King Jr. essay, undated (Box 9, Folder 254)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 9, Folder 255)
    - Untitled draft. Perhaps a fourth novel. Mystery featuring Detective Reese., undated (Box 9, Folder 256)
- Series VII: Personal Correspondence and Biographical Material
  This series is broken into five subseries. Subseries A contains letters from Heather Lewis organized alphabetically by the last name of the addressee. Subseries B contains letters to Heather Lewis where the first and last name of the sender is known. These materials are in alphabetical order by sender's last name. Subseries C contains letters to Heather Lewis from senders who only included first name. Materials are in alphabetical order. Subseries D includes letters to other people from other people, for example a letter to Allen Gurganus from Malaga Baldi. Finally, Subseries E includes biographical material about Heather Lewis's life. Again, these materials are in alphabetical order by recipient's last name.
  - Subseries A: From Heather
    - Heather Lewis to Malaga Baldi. Includes one unsent letter [handwritten]., ca. 1995 (Box 9, Folder 257)
    - Heather Lewis to Allan Gurganus, ca. 1990 (Box 9, Folder 258)
    - Heather Lewis to Meredith. Unopened, unsent, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 259)
    - Heather Lewis to Veena Oldenberg, unopened, unsent., 1996 (Box 9, Folder 260)
  - Subseries B: To Heather, first and last names
    - S.A., 1995 (Box 9, Folder 261)
    - Abrams, Linsey., 1991-1996 (Box 9, Folder 262)
    - J.B., 1973 (Box 9, Folder 263)
    - Baldi, Malaga, 1994-1995 (Box 9, Folder 264)
    - Cedering, Siv, 1978-1980 (Box 9, Folder 265)
    - Cooper, Jane, ca. 1994 (Box 9, Folder 265B)
    - Dermansky, Michael, undated (Box 9, Folder 266)
    - Doty, Jean Slaughter, ca. 1974 (Box 9, Folder 267)
    - Epes, Maria, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 268)
    - Gurganus, Allan, 1990-1993 (Box 9, Folder 269)
    - Harper, Harry H. [Heather's Godfather], 1965-1967 (Box 9, Folder 270)
    - Homes, A.M., 1996 (Box 10, Folder 271)
    - Ivers, Mitchell, undated (Box 10, Folder 272)
    - Lewis, Mrs. Hobart [Heather Lewis's mother], 1991-1995 (Box 10, Folder 273)
    - Peck, Dale, undated (Box 10, Folder 274)
    - Scholder, Amy, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 275)
    - Shipo, Ellen, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 276)
    - Smith, Kimberly, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 277)
    - Taormino, Tristan, ca. 1995 (Box 10, Folder 278)
    - Tsui, Kitty, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 279)
    - de Vestel, Mona, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 280)
    - Warnock, Kathleen, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 281)
  - Subseries C: To Heather, first name only
    - Aliyiia and Diana, undated (Box 10, Folder 282)
    - Ann, undated (Box 10, Folder 283)
    - Betsy, undated (Box 10, Folder 284)
    - Bob and Christine, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 285)
    - Breezer, undated (Box 10, Folder 286)
    - Christine, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 287)
    - Elizabeth, undated (Box 10, Folder 288)
    - Elizabeth P., 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 289)
    - Gloria, undated (Box 10, Folder 290)
    - Jamie, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 291)
    - Jen, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 292)
    - Louise, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 293)
    - Mark and Paul, undated (Box 10, Folder 294)
    - Sherry, undated (Box 10, Folder 295)
    - Stacy and Randy, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 296)
    - Miscellaneous unknown, undated (Box 10, Folder 297)
    - Envelopes, addressed, empty., undated (Box 10, Folder 298)
  - Subseries D: To Others, from others
    - To Allan Gurganus from Malaga, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 299)
    - To Ann Rower, condolences., 2002 (Box 10, Folder 300)
  - Subseries E: Biographical Materials
    - Alcoholics Anonymous and Adult Children of Alcoholics information, ca. 1988 (Box 10, Folder 301)
    - Biography, undated (Box 10, Folder 301B)
    - Documentation of difficulty with neighbor, undated (Box 10, Folder 302)
    - Heather Lewis's Memorial Service program. June 12, 2002, St. Marks Church New York, New York. (Box 10, Folder 303)
    - Place Card, Heather Lewis and Connie Jones., undated (Box 10, Folder 304)
    - Talking points for couples' therapy., undated (Box 10, Folder 305)
- Series VIII: Administrative Materials
  This series is broken into eleven subseries. Subseries A contains contracts for books and contributions arranged in chronological order. Subseries B includes royalty statements arranged in chronological order. Subseries C includes author photographs, some of Heather Lewis and some of other authors arranged alphabetically. Subseries D contains tax information arranged chronologically. Subseries E includes accounting, bills and statements from credit card companies, banks and other financial institutions. These materials are arranged chronologically. Subseries F contains administrative correspondence including letters from publishers, agents and fans. These materials are arranged alphabetically. Subseries G incorporates calendars and contacts such as day planners, business cards and phone lists. The subseries is arranged in chronological order. Subseries H includes resumes, applications and calls for papers arranged in alphabetical order. Subseries I holds materials related to Lewis's work instructing writing workshops. Materials are arranged chronologically. Subseries J includes promotional and journalistic materials on publishers arranged alphabetically. Suberies K contains miscellaneous materials.
  - Subseries A: Contracts
    - Doubleday contract, House Rules, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 306)
    - Memorandum of Agreement, Heather Lewis and Uitgerverij Anthos- Dutch publishers, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 307)
    - Contributor Agreement, 1,001 Things Everyone Should Know About Women's History, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 308)
    - Publishing Agreement, Best American Lesbian Erotica 1996, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 309)
    - Contract, Brook Altman and Heather Lewis, rights to House Rules., 1996 (Box 10, Folder 310)
    - Doubleday agreement, Restitution [became Second Suspect], 1996 (Box 10, Folder 311)
    - Doubleday contract with edits, Restitution, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 312)
    - Contract with Tristan Taormino for Best of Lesbian Erotica, undated (Box 10, Folder 313)
  - Subseries B: Royalties
    - Doubleday Royalties, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 314)
    - Doubleday Royalties, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 315)
    - Doubleday Royalties, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 316)
    - Random House and Reed Royalty Statements, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 317)
    - Doubleday Royalties, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 318)
    - Janklow and Nesbit Royalties, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 319)
    - Random House Royalty Statement, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 320)
  - Subseries C: Author Photos
    - Other authors and artists, undated (Box 10, Folder 321)
    - Heather Lewis postcards, photograph by Jill Krementz., 1996 (Box 10, Folder 322)
    - Heather Lewis, photographed by Jill Krementz, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 323)
    - Heather Lewis, photographed by Marion Ettlinger., undated (Box 10, Folder 324)
  - Subseries D: Taxes
    - Taxes, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 325)
    - Unicorp Business Tax return, NY City department of Finance., 1995 (Box 10, Folder 326)
    - Request for Tax Payment, IRS, 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 327)
    - Estimated tax 1040-ES(OCR) form, unopened, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 328)
    - Taxes, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 329)
    - Taxes, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 330)
    - Taxes, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 331)
  - Subseries E: Accounting, Bills and Statements
    - Bank Statements, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 332)
    - Accounting Ledger, 1989-1991 (Box 10, Folder 333)
    - Accounting Ledger, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 334)
    - Termination of medical insurance, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 335)
    - Credit card statements, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 336)
    - Credit card statements, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 337)
    - Receipts, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 337B)
    - Accounting ledger, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 338)
    - Credit card statements, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 339)
    - Receipts, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 340)
    - Rental car information, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 341)
    - Bank statements, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 342)
    - Credit card statements, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 343)
    - Receipts, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 344)
    - Credit card statements, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 345)
    - Receipts, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 345B)
    - Bank statements, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 346)
    - Bills, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 347)
    - Insurance, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 348)
    - Credit card statements, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 349)
    - Credit card information, general., undated (Box 10, Folder 350)
    - Financial planning notes., undated (Box 10, Folder 351)
    - PIN numbers, undated (Box 10, Folder 352)
  - Subseries F: Administrative Correspondence
    - Heather Lewis to Ann Bentley at Doubleday, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 353)
    - Heather Lewis to Jesse Cohen at Doubleday, undated (Box 10, Folder 354)
    - Heather Lewis to The Messenger, regarding Francis Randall, undated (Box 10, Folder 355)
    - Heather Lewis to Ira Silverberg, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 356)
    - Heather Lewis to Nan Talese, undated (Box 10, Folder 357)
    - Heather Lewis to Amanda Urban., 1997 (Box 10, Folder 358)
    - Abner Stein, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 359)
    - Abner Stein, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 360)
    - van Akin, Tracy (Box 10, Folder 361)
    - Alvarez, Anica. Martin Secker and Warburg, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 362)
    - Aft Forum, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 363)
    - Malaga Baldi Literary Agency, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 364)
    - Malaga Baldi Literary Agency, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 365)
    - Malaga Baldi Literary Agency, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 366)
    - Malaga Baldi Literary Agency, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 367)
    - Malaga Baldi Literary Agency, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 368)
    - Malaga Baldi Literary Agency, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 369)
    - Malaga Baldi Literary Agency, undated (Box 10, Folder 370)
    - Bentley, Ann. Doubleday, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 371)
    - Boston University Secial Collections, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 372)
    - Boyd, Eugenie. Martin Secker and Warburg, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 373)
    - Brooks, Alicia. Doubleday, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 374)
    - Cardinale, Marisa, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 375)
    - Chunilal, Tamsin. Martin Secker and Warburg, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 376)
    - Cohen, Jesse. Doubleday, 1993-1998 (Box 10, Folder 377)
    - Conde Nast Publications, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 378)
    - Contemporary Authors, undated (Box 10, Folder 379)
    - Daly, Meg, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 380)
    - Doyle, Suzanne, 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 381)
    - Eilenberg, Max. Martin Secker and Warburg, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 382)
    - 50/50 Magazine, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 383)
    - Ford, Michael Thomas, 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 384)
    - Janklow and Nesbit Associates, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 385)
    - Janklow and Nesbit Associates, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 386)
    - Janklow and Nesbit Associates, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 387)
    - Janklow and Nesbit Associates, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 388)
    - Koch, Stephen. Columbia University, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 389)
    - Mary Ingraham Bunting Institute of Radcliffe College, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 390)
    - Mattes, Jed, undated (Box 10, Folder 391)
    - Miller, Michael. Voice Literary Supplement, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 392)
    - PEN American Center, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 393)
    - Schinto, Jeanne, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 394)
    - Seventeen Magazine, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 395)
    - Silverberg, Ira. Serpent's Tail, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 396)
    - Smyth, Sarah. Martin Secker and Warburg, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 397)
    - Sosland, Cynthia, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 398)
    - Talese, Nan. Doubleday, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 399)
    - Urban, Amanda, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 400)
    - Weil, Wendy, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 401)
    - Witherspoon Associates, Inc., 1994 (Box 10, Folder 402)
    - Wylie, Aitken and Stone, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 403)
    - Yaddo, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 404)
    - Lenna [no last name], 2000 (Box 10, Folder 405)
    - Correspondence from readers, undated (Box 10, Folder 406)
  - Subseries G: Calendars and contacts
    - Business cards [other people's], undated (Box 10, Folder 407)
    - phone lists, undated (Box 10, Folder 408)
    - Day planner calendar, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 409)
    - Day planner calendar, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 410)
    - Day planner calendar, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 411)
    - Day planner calendar, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 412)
  - Subseries H: Resumes, applications, calls for papers
    - Resume, undated (Box 11, Folder 413)
    - Fellowship application statement of purpose, undated (Box 11, Folder 414)
    - Proof reading applications, 1991-1995 (Box 11, Folder 415)
    - Calls for papers, potential projects, undated (Box 11, Folder 416)
  - Subseries I: Writing Workshops
    - "Y Workshop", 1987 (Box 11, Folder 417)
    - Writing workshop, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 418)
    - Outwrite, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 419)
    - Writer's Voice, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 420)
    - Dialogue with yourself by Ira Progoff, undated (Box 11, Folder 421)
    - Mundis Notes, undated (Box 11, Folder 422)
    - Poetry vocabulary, undated (Box 11, Folder 423)
    - Presentation, undated (Box 11, Folder 424)
    - Screenplay notes, undated (Box 11, Folder 425)
    - Typewriter settings, undated (Box 11, Folder 426)
  - Subseries J: Publisher Files
    - Bertelsmann, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 427)
    - Ordfront Publishing House, Stockholm, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 428)
    - Reed Publishing, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 429)
    - Swanson Literary Agency, undated (Box 11, Folder 430)
  - Subseries K: Miscellaneous
    - Ardache Corporation Board of Directors Meeting [Ann Rower], 1994-1997 (Box 11, Folder 431)
    - MNN certificate of Completion, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 432)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 11, Folder 433)
- Series IX: Research